

Veer Pariawala

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

pariawalaveer@gmail.com

9833693702

Mumbai, India

github.com/VP45

I am a passionate person when it comes to designing and art. I've been a graphic designer for more than two years, been able to channel my innovative skills from Photoshop to Figma in the past couple of months in order to become a front end web developer. Being able to adapt to collaborative environments along with having a healthy working culture are one of the key attributes I bring along with me.

EDUCATION

B.E in Information Technology (Pursuing)

Thadomal Shahani Engineering College

01/2021 - Present Mumbai, India

HSC (12th Board)

Pace Junior Science College, Dadar

06/2018 - 05/2020 Mumbai, India

PCM (Science)

- 91.84%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Design Executive

Ellement Co. 🗷

07/2023 - Present Sin

"Ellement Co. offers a wide range of premium beauty products and aspiring nail technicians through their esteemed academy."

Task.

 Establishing brand guidelines for their academy, and handling social media posts, flyers, coverbooks.

Front-End Web Developer Intern

Claxon Tournaments Pte. Ltd

03/2023 - Present Singapore

Claxon Tournaments Pte. Ltd. is an events management company based in Singapore which hosts esports events across the globe.

Task

 A website related to the tournaments hosted by the company weekly along with blogs/insights.

Design DirectorCompact Esports

01/2022 - 05/2023

Finland, Europe

Singapore

Compact Esports is a tournament management company based in Finland which hosts Critical Ops events across the globe.

Tasks

Leading all designers through the past 3 "Circuit'
 Seasons, which were conducted from Jan 2022 to Jan 2023, along with designing the assets for the same.

Creative Manager

Claxon Tournaments Pte. Ltd.

04/2021 - 04/2022

Claxon Tournaments Pte. Ltd. is an events management company based in Singapore which hosts esports events across the globe.

Achievements/Tasks

 Managing the company for various design requirements and establishing a brand guide.

SKILLS

HTML CSS JS Typescript React JS

Next JS Tailwind CSS C++ Python

Machine Learning Adobe Photoshop Figma

PROJECTS

BidBazaar (Auction-Bid website) (05/2023 - 05/2023)

 BidBazaar is an auction bidding website that offers a platform for buyers and sellers to participate in online auctions. With features like live chat, auction history, and a FAQ section for each auction, users can bid on a wide range of products, including tenders electronics, etc. Our ML models suggest initial auction biddings to the product owner, ensuring fair and reasonable bidding prices.

FlyCast (ML Based Website) (02/2023 - 04/2023) 🗗

 FlyCast is a website for Indian flight price predictions based on a customized search form, and having a trip planner along with it with the help of AI, and ease of use through the UI.

Cryptoverse (Redux Toolkit API based website) (02/2023 - 03/2023) ♂

 Cryptoverse is a website solely based on Redux Toolkit implementation for API Queries, and is based on real-time crypto market data exchanges, rates, news and each crypto currency current value deviation with more meatures.

Kartify (E-commerce Website) (08/2022 - 10/2022) ☑

 Kartify is an ecommerce website similar to Amazon, Flipkart and other websites, having features such as buying products, having payment gateway through Stripe, automated invoice generation and mailed to clients, along with more features.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Gujarati

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

ACHIEVEMENTS

TIAA Intercollege 2023 Winners

Top 10 Placement in KJSCE 2.0 National Hackathon

Creative of the Quarter at Rotaract District Mumbai